var questions;

questions = [
    {
        number: 0,
        question: 'Who lived at 25 Cromwell Street?',
        choices: ['Jack the Ripper', 'Ian Bradley and Myra Hindley', 'Fred and Rose West', 'The Yorkshire Ripper'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        number: 1,
        question: 'How did Ted Bundy lure his victims in?',
        choices: ['Pretending to be an officer', 'Pretending to be injured', 'Asking them out on a date', 'Knocking them out'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        number: 2,
        question: 'What year was the term "serial killer" coined in America?',
        choices: ['1912', '1996', '1960', '1976'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        number: 3,
        question: 'What cult inspired Timothy McReign, the Oklahoma City Bomber, to do what he did?',
        choices: ['The Branen Dividians', 'Children of God', 'The Manson Family', 'Aum Shinrikyo'],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        number: 4,
        question: 'How many people did Ed Gein kill?',
        choices: ['10', '25', '2', '6'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        number: 5,
        question: 'How many was Ed Gein convicted for?',
        choices: ['0', '1', '10', '16'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        number: 6,
        question: 'What was Brenda Spencer\'s reason for her killing spree at Cleveland Elementary School?',
        choices: ['She didn\'t like Mondays', 'She was being bullied', 'She wanted to see what killing was like', 'She hated kids'],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        number: 7,
        question: 'What does Dennis Rader\'s nickname, "BTK", stand for?',
        choices: ['Bind, Torture, Kill', 'Blindfold, Tickle, Kill', 'Bind, Tickle, Kill', 'Blindfold, Torture, Kill'],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        number: 8,
        question: 'What was Sacramento serial killer Richard Chase\'s nickname?',
        choices: ['The Night Stalker', 'The Vampire of Sacramento', 'The East Area Rapist', 'The Zodiac Killer'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        number: 9,
        question: 'Which woman was thought to be the first serial killer?',
        choices: ['Aileen Wuornos', 'Belle Gunness', 'Jane Toppan', 'Lavinia Fisher'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        number: 10,
        question: 'What book was the torn page from that was found with the Somerton Man?',
        choices: ['The Rudaiyat of Omar Khayyan', 'The Bible', 'The Great Gatsby', 'The Quaran'],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        number: 11,
        question: 'How many years was Jaycee LeeDugard held against her own will?',
        choices: ['1 year', '8 years', '25 years', '3 years'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        number: 12,
        question: 'What disorder did the Eriksson Twins suffer from?',
        choices: ['Bipolar', 'Schizophrenia', 'Depression', 'Folie a deux'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        number: 13,
        question: 'What country was the infamous "Who put Bella in the wych-elm" body found?',
        choices: ['England', 'Ireland', 'Scotland', 'Poland'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        number: 14,
        question: 'What was John Wayne Gacy known as?',
        choices: ['The Killer Clown', 'The Midwest Killer', 'The Hillside Strangler', 'The Candyman'],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        number: 15,
        question: 'Who was Leonard Lake\'s partner in crime?',
        choices: ['Dean Corll', 'Charles Ng', 'David Burkowitz', 'Ottis Toole'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        number: 16,
        question: 'What country did Andrei Chikatilo hail from?',
        choices: ['England', 'Japan', 'America', 'Russia'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        number: 17,
        question: 'What state was The Green River Killer active in?',
        choices: ['Ohio', 'New York', 'California', 'Washington'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        number: 18,
        question: 'Who was known to be Jack the Ripper\'s last victim?',
        choices: ['Martha Tabram', 'Catherine Eddowes', 'Mary Ann Nichols', 'Mary Kelly'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        number: 19,
        question: 'What was the movie The Zodiac Killer referred to as the best satirical comedy?',
        choices: ['The Exorcist', 'Halloween', 'Jaws', 'Amityville Horror'],
        answer: 0
    }
];